ELLYA AISYAH

FRONT END DEVELOPER

Email

ellyaaisyah@gmail.com

PROFILE INFO

I am a Front End developer with 7 years of experience building web applications using several JavaScript frameworks. I specialize in creating modern, responsive and easy to use web experiences. I'm also able to productively work independently as well as effectively collaborate within a team.

MY SKILLS

HTML5, CSS3, Sass/LESS, JavaScript/TypeScript, React, React Router, React Query, React Testing Library, Jest, Bootstrap

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front End Developer

2019 - present

Drieam

- Implemented a student led and assessment portfolio web application.
- Refactored an AngularJS LTI application to ReactJS.
- Assessed and refined UI and UX designs for technical feasibility.
- Implemented contextual learning and gamification of Canvas courses.

Freelance Web Developer

2018 - 2020

Institute SI

- Implemented a responsive website using VueJS.
- Built a CMS tool to manage the content of the website.
- Used Firebase to manage all data of the website.

Front End Developer

2015 - 2019

GameHouse

- · Implementing designers's concept to life.
- Revamped the layout of an outdated website using recent technologies.
- Developed a catalogue hybrid app using Ionic Framework which also includes a card collecting meta game.
- Implemented an in-game experience for users to be able to purchase GameHouse subscription model.

EDUCATION HISTORY